(function(){var e={8177:function(e){e.exports=[{itemName:"jobCenter-office",settingName:"jobCenter",vignette_start:"You are working at the job center consultation desk and help people find open vacancies. Please type ‘teacher’ in the text area. Currently the following positions are available at local businesses:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"had",question:"Is there an open accountant job?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no accountant job open.",answer_template:"There is *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"an accountant job",competitor:"a bookkeeper job",sameCategory:"a manager assistant job",otherCategory:"a car mechanic job",correct_response:"teacher"},{itemName:"jobCenter-engineer",settingName:"jobCenter",vignette_start:"You are working at the job center consultation desk and help people find open vacancies. Please type ‘teacher’ in the text area. Currently the following positions are available at local businesses:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"had",question:"Is there an electrical mechanic job open?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, there is no electrical mechanic job open.",answer_template:"There is *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"an electrical mechanic job",competitor:"an electrician job",sameCategory:"a car mechanic job",otherCategory:"a secretary job",correct_response:"teacher"},{itemName:"art-painting",settingName:"art",vignette_start:"You work at an art shop. You are hosting an exhibition sale by a local artist. The artist has",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘sculpture’ in the text area. \\n\\nA customer takes a look around and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Are there any acrylic paintings for sale?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, there are no acrylic paintings.",answer_template:"There are *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"acrylic paintings",competitor:"gouache paintings",sameCategory:"oil paintings",otherCategory:"pencil drawings",correct_response:"sculpture"},{itemName:"art-drawing",settingName:"art",vignette_start:"You work at an art shop. You are hosting an exhibition sale by a local artist. The artist has",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘sculpture’ in the text area. \\n\\nA customer takes a look around and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Are there any ink drawings for sale?",taciturn:"I’m sorry, there are no ink drawings.",answer_template:"There are *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"ink drawings",competitor:"pencil drawings",sameCategory:"crayon drawings",otherCategory:"oil paintings",correct_response:"sculpture"},{itemName:"carRental-fun",settingName:"carRental",vignette_start:"You are working in a private car rental agency. Please type ‘motorcycle’ in the text area. For today, the following types of vehicles are still available on site:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Do you have a Porsche for rent today?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have a Porsche on site today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"a Porsche",competitor:"a Ferrari",sameCategory:"a BMW convertible",otherCategory:"a medium-sized delivery truck",correct_response:"motorcycle"},{itemName:"carRental-moving",settingName:"carRental",vignette_start:"You are working in a private car rental agency. Please type ‘motorcycle’ in the text area. For today, the following types of vehicles are still available on site:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nA young man walks in and asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to have",priorElicitation_question:"got",question:"Is a moving truck available on site?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don’t have a moving truck on site today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"a moving truck",competitor:"a medium-sized delivery truck",sameCategory:"a Volkswagen camper",otherCategory:"a Ferrari",correct_response:"motorcycle"},{itemName:"music-hardrock",settingName:"music",vignette_start:"You are driving in a car with your neighbor. Please type ‘classic’ in the text area. The car only has an old CD player. You have the following styles of music:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to listen to",priorElicitation_question:"listened to",question:"Do you have any hard rock?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have any hard rock.",answer_template:"I have some *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"hard rock",competitor:"classic rock",sameCategory:"heavy metal",otherCategory:"cool jazz",correct_response:"classic"},{itemName:"music-softrock",settingName:"music",vignette_start:"You are driving in a car with your neighbor. Please type ‘classic’ in the text area. The car only has an old CD player. You have the following styles of music:",vignette_continuation:"\\n\\nYour neighbor asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the right. Suppose someone wants to listen to",priorElicitation_question:"listened to",question:"Do you have any soft rock?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, I don't have any soft rock.",answer_template:"I have some *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"soft rock",competitor:"cool jazz",sameCategory:"soul jazz",otherCategory:"death metal",correct_response:"classic"},{itemName:"airport-usa",settingName:"airport",vignette_start:"You are a customer service agent helping to book flights. Today there is ",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘London’ in the text area.\\n\\nA customer asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to book",priorElicitation_question:"booked",question:"Do you have an afternoon flight to Boston?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have an afternoon flight to Boston today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"an afternoon flight to Boston",competitor:"a morning flight to Boston",sameCategory:"an afternoon flight to San Francisco",otherCategory:"a flight to Australia",correct_response:"London"},{itemName:"airport-europe-UPDATED",settingName:"airport",vignette_start:"You are a customer service agent helping to book flights. Today there is",vignette_continuation:"Please type ‘London’ in the text area.\\n\\nA customer asks:",priorElicitation_context:"Please move all sliders all the way to the left. Suppose someone wants to book",priorElicitation_question:"booked",question:"Do you have a morning flight to Madrid?",taciturn:"I'm sorry, we don't have a morning flight to Madrid today.",answer_template:"We have *.",type:"filler",itemQuestion:"a morning flight to Madrid",competitor:"a morning flight to Barcelona with connections to other airports",sameCategory:"an evening flight to Paris",otherCategory:"a flight to New York",correct_response:"London"}]},5659:function(e){e.exports=[{"":0,itemName:"blanket-sleepover",settingName:"blanket",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone hosts a sleepover and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a blanket",competitor:"a sleeping bag",sameCategory:"bubble wrap",mostSimilar:"a pillow",otherCategory:"a carpet",correct_response:"main"},{"":1,itemName:"blanket-transportation",settingName:"blanket",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone has to transport a mirror and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a blanket",competitor:"bubble wrap",sameCategory:"a sleeping bag",mostSimilar:"a pillow",otherCategory:"a carpet",correct_response:"main"},{"":2,itemName:"box-muffins",settingName:"box",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to take home some muffins and asks for a ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a box",competitor:"a cake container",sameCategory:"a ziplock bag",mostSimilar:"a carton",otherCategory:"a tote bag",correct_response:"main"},{"":3,itemName:"box-bbq",settingName:"box",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to take home BBQ leftovers and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a box",competitor:"a ziplock bag",sameCategory:"a cake container",mostSimilar:"a carton",otherCategory:"a tote bag",correct_response:"main"},{"":4,itemName:"sugar-coffee",settingName:"sugar",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone wants to sweeten their coffee and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"sugar",competitor:"sweetener tablets",sameCategory:"agave syrup",mostSimilar:"honey",otherCategory:"salt",correct_response:"main"},{"":5,itemName:"sugar-baking",settingName:"sugar",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to bake and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"sugar",competitor:"agave syrup",sameCategory:"sweetener tablets",mostSimilar:"honey",otherCategory:"salt",correct_response:"main"},{"":6,itemName:"handkerchief-injury",settingName:"handkerchief",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone helps a child who just fell down and hurt their knee and asks for  ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a handkerchief",competitor:"band aids",sameCategory:"wet wipes",mostSimilar:"paper napkins",otherCategory:"a cell phone",correct_response:"main"},{"":7,itemName:"handkerchief-sauce",settingName:"handkerchief",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone spilled sauce on their sweater and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a handkerchief",competitor:"wet wipes",sameCategory:"band aids",mostSimilar:"paper napkins",otherCategory:"a cell phone",correct_response:"main"},{"":8,itemName:"broom-renovation",settingName:"broom",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone cleans their apartment after a renovation and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a broom",competitor:"vacuum cleaner",sameCategory:"shovel",mostSimilar:"a hand brush",otherCategory:"a lamp",correct_response:"main"},{"":9,itemName:"broom-snow",settingName:"broom",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to clean snow off a driveway and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a broom",competitor:"shovel",sameCategory:"vacuum cleaner",mostSimilar:"a hand brush",otherCategory:"a lamp",correct_response:"main"},{"":10,itemName:"sweatpants-sleepover",settingName:"sweatpants",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is staying for a sleepover and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a pair of sweatpants",competitor:"pyjamas",sameCategory:"shorts",mostSimilar:"a pair of leggings",otherCategory:"towels",correct_response:"main"},{"":11,itemName:"sweatpants-spill",settingName:"sweatpants",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone spilled coffee on their pants at a garden party and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a pair of sweatpants",competitor:"shorts",sameCategory:"pyjamas",mostSimilar:"a pair of leggings",otherCategory:"towels",correct_response:"main"},{"":12,itemName:"umbrella-summer",settingName:"umbrella",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to spend time outside in the garden on a sunny day and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"an umbrella",competitor:"sunscreen",sameCategory:"a rain jacket",mostSimilar:"a plastic bike cover",otherCategory:"a tent",correct_response:"main"},{"":13,itemName:"umbrella-rain",settingName:"umbrella",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to leave the house during a heavy rain and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"an umbrella",competitor:"a rain jacket",sameCategory:"sunscreen",mostSimilar:"a plastic bike cover",otherCategory:"a tent",correct_response:"main"},{"":14,itemName:"postit-board",settingName:"postit",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is organizing a workshop around a whiteboard and asks for    ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"post-its",competitor:"a whiteboard marker",sameCategory:"sticky bookmarks",mostSimilar:"a notebook",otherCategory:"an eraser",correct_response:"main"},{"":15,itemName:"postit-reading",settingName:"postit",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone reads through a lot of documents and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"post-its",competitor:"sticky bookmarks",sameCategory:"a whiteboard marker",mostSimilar:"a notebook",otherCategory:"an eraser",correct_response:"main"},{"":16,itemName:"pot-garden",settingName:"pot",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is repotting their garden plants and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a pot",competitor:"old cans",sameCategory:"camping cookware",mostSimilar:"a pan",otherCategory:"ceramic plates",correct_response:"main"},{"":17,itemName:"pot-jam",settingName:"pot",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is cooking apple jam in their garden and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a pot",competitor:"camping cookware",sameCategory:"old cans",mostSimilar:"a pan",otherCategory:"ceramic plates",correct_response:"main"},{"":18,itemName:"towel-hair",settingName:"towel",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone got into a heavy rain on their way to a Halloween party and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a towel",competitor:"a hair dryer",sameCategory:"a dryer",mostSimilar:"paper towels",otherCategory:"a blanket",correct_response:"main"},{"":19,itemName:"towel-clothes",settingName:"towel",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone got into a heavy rain on their way to a Halloween party and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a towel",competitor:"a dryer",sameCategory:"a hair dryer",mostSimilar:"paper towels",otherCategory:"a blanket",correct_response:"main"},{"":20,itemName:"candy-halloween",settingName:"candy",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to give out treats to kids on Halloween and asks for  ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"candy",competitor:"little trail mix packages",sameCategory:"ice cream",mostSimilar:"a big chocolate bar",otherCategory:"soda",correct_response:"main"},{"":21,itemName:"candy-dessert",settingName:"candy",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone finished dinner and asks for  ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"candy",competitor:"ice cream",sameCategory:"little trail mix packages",mostSimilar:"a big chocolate bar",otherCategory:"soda",correct_response:"main"},{"":22,itemName:"bottle-plants",settingName:"bottle",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is about to water plants at their office and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a bottle",competitor:"a watering can",sameCategory:"a to-go mug",mostSimilar:"a glass",otherCategory:"a spoon",correct_response:"main"},{"":23,itemName:"bottle-water",settingName:"bottle",priorElicitation_context:"Suppose someone is preparing for a long walk during a hot day and asks for ",priorElicitation_question:"got",itemQuestion:"a bottle",competitor:"a to-go mug",sameCategory:"a watering can",mostSimilar:"a glass",otherCategory:"a spoon",correct_response:"main"}]},9446:function(e,t,o){"use strict";var a=o(5471),i=o(4302),r=o.n(i),n=o(6093),s=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Experiment",{attrs:{title:"question-answering-experiment"}},[t("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Welcome"}},[e._v(" Thank you for taking part in our experiment! "),t("br"),e._v(" You are participating in a study conducted by cognitive scientists at the University of Tübingen. Your participation in this research is voluntary. You may decline to answer any or all of the following questions. You may decline further participation, at any time, without adverse consequences."),t("br"),e._v(" The experiment will take approximately 3-4 minutes. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Your anonymity is assured; the researchers who have requested your participation will not receive any personal information about you. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" By pressing the button 'Next' you confirm that you are at least 18 years old and agree to participate in this study. ")]),t("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Instructions"}},[e._v(" In this study we are interested in how you think about other people. On each trial, you will be given some information about a person, for example: 'Suppose someone wants to have Italian food.' "),t("br"),e._v(" Then we'll ask how happy you think this person would be about other things, given this information. For instance, we might ask: 'How happy do you think they would be if they had French food instead?' You'll use sliders to answer the questions. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(' Sometimes you might think that the person will be very happy with the option they receive, in which case you should move the slider towards the option "completely happy". For other trials, you might think that they will not be very happy, in which case you should move the slider towards the option "completely unhappy". On trials where you think the person is neither happy nor unhappy, please adjust the slider around the middle. '),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Notice that there will also be simple "),t("b",[e._v("attention checking trials")]),e._v(". You will recognize them immediately when you read the important text on each trial carefully -- those trials contain instructions for you to "),t("b",[e._v("move the sliders in a certain way")]),e._v(". Please follow these instructions on the respective trial. "),t("br"),t("br"),e._v(" Please try to respond naturally and reasonably, do not overthink your ratings. "),t("br")]),e._l(e.trials,(function(o,a){return[2==o.length?[t("ParallelRatingScreen",{key:a,attrs:{trial:o[0],index:a,trial_type:"main",targetOption:o[1],progress:a/e.trials.length,itemOrder:e._.shuffle(["competitor","mostSimilar","sameCategory","otherCategory","itemQuestion"])}})]:[t("ParallelRatingScreen",{key:a,attrs:{trial:o,index:a,trial_type:"filler",targetOption:"itemQuestion",progress:a/e.trials.length,itemOrder:e._.shuffle(["competitor","sameCategory","otherCategory","itemQuestion"])}})]]})),t("PostTestScreen"),t("SubmitResultsScreen")],2)},l=[],c=o(2543),m=o.n(c),p=o(5659),u=o.n(p),h=o(8177),g=o.n(h),d=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Screen",{attrs:{progress:e.progress}},[t("Slide",[t("Record",{attrs:{data:{trialNr:e.index+1,itemName:e.trial.itemName,settingName:e.trial.settingName,trial_type:e.trial_type,itemOrder:e.itemOrder.join(","),targetOption:e.targetOption}}}),t("span",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.createContext(e.trial,e.targetOption))}}),t("p",[e._v("How happy do you think they would be if...")]),t("br"),t("span",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.createAnswerOption(e.trial,e.itemOrder[0],e.targetOption))}}),t("SliderInput",{attrs:{left:"completely unhappy",right:"completely happy",initial:"50",response:e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[0]]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,e.itemOrder[0],t)}}}),t("span",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.createAnswerOption(e.trial,e.itemOrder[1],e.targetOption))}}),t("SliderInput",{attrs:{left:"completely unhappy",right:"completely happy",initial:"50",response:e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[1]]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,e.itemOrder[1],t)}}}),t("span",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.createAnswerOption(e.trial,e.itemOrder[2],e.targetOption))}}),t("SliderInput",{attrs:{left:"completely unhappy",right:"completely happy",initial:"50",response:e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[2]]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,e.itemOrder[2],t)}}}),t("span",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.createAnswerOption(e.trial,e.itemOrder[3],e.targetOption))}}),t("SliderInput",{attrs:{left:"completely unhappy",right:"completely happy",initial:"50",response:e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[3]]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,e.itemOrder[3],t)}}}),t("span",{domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(e.createAnswerOption(e.trial,e.itemOrder[4],e.targetOption))}}),t("SliderInput",{attrs:{left:"completely unhappy",right:"completely happy",initial:"50",response:e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[4]]},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,e.itemOrder[4],t)}}}),e.checkResponses(e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[0]],e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[1]],e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[2]],e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[3]],e.$magpie.measurements[e.itemOrder[4]])?t("button",{on:{click:function(t){return e.$magpie.saveAndNextScreen()}}},[e._v(" Submit ")]):e._e()],1)],1)},y=[];function f(e,t){var o=e[t],a=[e["priorElicitation_context"]," <b>",o,".</b>"].join("");return a}function b(e,t,o){if(o==t)var a=e[t],i=["<br/>","... they actually ",e["priorElicitation_question"]," <b>",a,"</b>?"].join("");else a=e[t],i=["<br/>","... they ",e["priorElicitation_question"]," <b>",a,"</b> instead?"].join("");return i}var v={name:"ParallelRatingScreen",data(){return{response:0}},props:{trial:{type:Object,required:!0},index:{type:Number,required:!0},trial_type:{type:String,required:!0},progress:{type:Number,default:void 0},itemOrder:{type:Array,required:!0},targetOption:{type:String,required:!0}},methods:{checkResponses:function(e,t,o,a){return!(isNaN(e)|isNaN(t)|isNaN(o)|isNaN(a))},createAnswerOption:b,createContext:f}},_=v,w=o(1656),k=(0,w.A)(_,d,y,!1,null,null,null),C=k.exports,S=m().sample(["odd","even"]);const N=5,x=1,E="even"==S?u().filter(((e,t)=>t%2==0)):u().filter(((e,t)=>t%2!=0)),q=m().sampleSize(E,N),O=m().shuffle(["competitor","mostSimilar","sameCategory","otherCategory","itemQuestion"]),j=m().zip(q,O);console.log("trails_w_target"),console.log(q),console.log("targets ",O),console.log(j);const P="odd"==S?g().filter(((e,t)=>t%2===0)):g().filter(((e,t)=>t%2!=0));document.onselectstart=()=>!1,document.oncontextmenu=()=>!1;var Q={name:"App",components:{ParallelRatingScreen:C},data(){return{trials:m().shuffle(m().concat(j,m().sampleSize(P,x)))}},computed:{_(){return m()}}},T=Q,A=(0,w.A)(T,s,l,!1,null,null,null),I=A.exports,Y={experimentId:"22",serverUrl:"https://magpie-cogsciprag.fly.dev//",socketUrl:"wss://magpie-cogsciprag.fly.dev//socket",completionUrl:"https://app.prolific.co/submissions/complete?cc=CT0J8WXX",contactEmail:"polina.tsvilodub@uni-tuebingen.de",mode:"directLink",language:"en"};a["default"].config.productionTip=!1,a["default"].use(r(),{prefix:"Canvas"}),a["default"].use(n.Ay,Y),new a["default"]({render:e=>e(I)}).$mount("#app")}},t={};function o(a){var i=t[a];if(void 0!==i)return i.exports;var r=t[a]={id:a,loaded:!1,exports:{}};return e[a].call(r.exports,r,r.exports,o),r.loaded=!0,r.exports}o.m=e,function(){var e=[];o.O=function(t,a,i,r){if(!a){var n=1/0;for(m=0;m<e.length;m++){a=e[m][0],i=e[m][1],r=e[m][2];for(var s=!0,l=0;l<a.length;l++)(!1&r||n>=r)&&Object.keys(o.O).every((function(e){return o.O[e](a[l])}))?a.splice(l--,1):(s=!1,r<n&&(n=r));if(s){e.splice(m--,1);var c=i();void 0!==c&&(t=c)}}return t}r=r||0;for(var m=e.length;m>0&&e[m-1][2]>r;m--)e[m]=e[m-1];e[m]=[a,i,r]}}(),function(){o.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return o.d(t,{a:t}),t}}(),function(){o.d=function(e,t){for(var a in t)o.o(t,a)&&!o.o(e,a)&&Object.defineProperty(e,a,{enumerable:!0,get:t[a]})}}(),function(){o.f={},o.e=function(e){return Promise.all(Object.keys(o.f).reduce((function(t,a){return o.f[a](e,t),t}),[]))}}(),function(){o.u=function(e){return"js/"+e+".71db2635.js"}}(),function(){o.miniCssF=function(e){}}(),function(){o.g=function(){if("object"===typeof globalThis)return globalThis;try{return this||new Function("return this")()}catch(e){if("object"===typeof window)return window}}()}(),function(){o.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)}}(),function(){var e={},t="test:";o.l=function(a,i,r,n){if(e[a])e[a].push(i);else{var s,l;if(void 0!==r)for(var c=document.getElementsByTagName("script"),m=0;m<c.length;m++){var p=c[m];if(p.getAttribute("src")==a||p.getAttribute("data-webpack")==t+r){s=p;break}}s||(l=!0,s=document.createElement("script"),s.charset="utf-8",s.timeout=120,o.nc&&s.setAttribute("nonce",o.nc),s.setAttribute("data-webpack",t+r),s.src=a),e[a]=[i];var u=function(t,o){s.onerror=s.onload=null,clearTimeout(h);var i=e[a];if(delete e[a],s.parentNode&&s.parentNode.removeChild(s),i&&i.forEach((function(e){return e(o)})),t)return t(o)},h=setTimeout(u.bind(null,void 0,{type:"timeout",target:s}),12e4);s.onerror=u.bind(null,s.onerror),s.onload=u.bind(null,s.onload),l&&document.head.appendChild(s)}}}(),function(){o.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})}}(),function(){o.nmd=function(e){return e.paths=[],e.children||(e.children=[]),e}}(),function(){o.p="/magpie3-qa-overinfo-free-production/experiments/05-contextSensitive-prior_elicitation/"}(),function(){var e={524:0};o.f.j=function(t,a){var i=o.o(e,t)?e[t]:void 0;if(0!==i)if(i)a.push(i[2]);else{var r=new Promise((function(o,a){i=e[t]=[o,a]}));a.push(i[2]=r);var n=o.p+o.u(t),s=new Error,l=function(a){if(o.o(e,t)&&(i=e[t],0!==i&&(e[t]=void 0),i)){var r=a&&("load"===a.type?"missing":a.type),n=a&&a.target&&a.target.src;s.message="Loading chunk "+t+" failed.\n("+r+": "+n+")",s.name="ChunkLoadError",s.type=r,s.request=n,i[1](s)}};o.l(n,l,"chunk-"+t,t)}},o.O.j=function(t){return 0===e[t]};var t=function(t,a){var i,r,n=a[0],s=a[1],l=a[2],c=0;if(n.some((function(t){return 0!==e[t]}))){for(i in s)o.o(s,i)&&(o.m[i]=s[i]);if(l)var m=l(o)}for(t&&t(a);c<n.length;c++)r=n[c],o.o(e,r)&&e[r]&&e[r][0](),e[r]=0;return o.O(m)},a=self["webpackChunktest"]=self["webpackChunktest"]||[];a.forEach(t.bind(null,0)),a.push=t.bind(null,a.push.bind(a))}();var a=o.O(void 0,[504],(function(){return o(9446)}));a=o.O(a)})();
//# sourceMappingURL=app.2e69f8d6.js.map